Guide to the Yale School of Medicine Student Class Notes
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale School of Medicine student class notes
1925-1928
RU 355
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
(1 box)
The records consist of the notes of Robert N. Taylor, who graduated from Yale Sheffield Scientific School in 1926 and Yale Medical School in 1930.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 47 (YRG 47), Collections documenting teaching and learning in Yale academic programs.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of the notes of Robert N. Taylor, who graduated from Yale Sheffield Scientific School in 1926 and Yale Medical School in 1930.
Medical students; Medicine -- Study and teaching; Taylor, Robert Nelson, 1903-; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. School of Medicine
- Class notes, 1925-1928; Accession 1994-A-082
  - C. J. McCormack, Physiological Chemistry, Yale Medical School, 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Case notes: Dr. Soper, Dr. Thomson, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Principles of pathology: Dr. Hussey, Dr. Winternitz, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Pharmacology: Dr. Underhill, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Bacteriology: Dr. Smith, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - C.M.S.: Dr. Burr, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bacteriology: Dr. Smith, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Autonomic nervous system: Dr. Stormout; physiology of nutrition: Dr. Cowgill, Dr. Smith, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Biochemical methods: Dr. Leonard, Dr. Underhill, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Notes on German, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Exam booklet, class hand-outs, loose note, circa 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 10)